Caleb Gibbs Web Developer

- 022 436 3494
- caleb@calebgibbsdev.com
- www.calebgibbsdev.com
- github.com/calebgibbs

CIRRICULUM VITAE



Personal Summary

My name is Caleb Gibbs. I am a recent graduate from Yoobee School of Design with a Diploma in Web Development. I have been creating websites for friends and family for the passed several years which has allowed me to improve my development skills and gain work experience. I am very confident using basic web-based languages such as; HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. I am also very efficient using software such as; Adobe Photoshop, InDesign and Illustrator.



Technical Skills

- HTML5 - Git - MySQL

- Adobe Photoshop - CSS3 - Ajax - JavaScript - Wordpress - Adobe Illustrator - Responsive Design - PHP - Adobe InDesign

- C++ - Sketch - Bootstrap



Soft Skills

- Communication skills - Works well in teams

- Quick learner - Desire to learn

- Strong work ethic - Time managment skills

- Adaptability - Open to constructive criticism



Education

Yoobee School of Design 2016

Diploma Of Web Development

2015 Wellington Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Information Technology

Heretaunga College 2010 - 2014 NCEA Levels 1, 2, 3



Employment

NZCIS Living & Giving **Briscoes Lower Hutt** 2016 - Present 2015 - 2016 2015 - 2016 -House keeping -Sales Assistant -Reception -Supervisor

-Checkins -Web packing and shipping

-Tech Support

2015 - 2016

Pikpok (voluntary work) **Rebel Sport**

-Sales Assistant -Help desk support

-Web packing and shipping -Website development

-Game testing

-Sales Assistant

-Duty Manager

Orbit Cleaning 2011 - 2013

Commerical Cleaning



Interests

I love language. To date I have studied Mandarin, Russian and Arabic. I love learning about different culture and meeting new people from different places. I really enjoy listening to different types of music, hiking and socialising with friends.

